https://www.carhartt.com/content/carhartt-privacy-policy

Skip to Content>>
×
YOU ARE ABOUT TO VISIT THE EUROPEAN SITE
Leaving the site? You are about to visit the European site which is intended for European residents, any changes you made to your cart may not be saved. Click continue to visit the European site or cancel to stay on the current site.
Order placed on the European site can only be delivered within Europe.
CONTINUE
CANCEL
×
We're having trouble creating your loyalty account. Please try again later or contact customer service at 1800.833.3118 for assistance.
×
Your session has timed out and you have been successfully logged off. Click Log in to access the store again.
Log in
Continue as Guest
Order Status
ORDER STATUS
Either the Order ID or the Email Address entered is incorrect. Enter the information again.
Order number
EMAIL
SUBMIT
×
LOYALTY
United States
North America
United States
Shop All Kids
Baby Boy (0-24M)
Baby Boy (0-24M)
Outerwear
Bib Overalls
Bottoms
Bodyshirts
Sets
Accessories
Baby Girl (0-24M)
Baby Girl (0-24M)
Accessories
Bib Overalls
Bottoms
Outerwear
Sets
Bodyshirts
Toddler Boy (2T-4T)
Toddler Boy (2T-4T)
Outerwear
Bib Overalls
Bottoms
Tops
Accessories
Toddler Girl (2T-4T)
Toddler Girl (2T-4T)
Accessories
Outerwear
Bib Overalls
Bottoms
Tops
Boy (4-16)
Boy (4-16)
Outerwear
Bottoms
Bib Overalls
Tops
Accessories
Hoodies & Sweatshirts
Girl (4-14)
Girl (4-14)
Bib Overalls
Outerwear
Bottoms
Tops
Accessories
Collections
Collections
Holiday Collection
Founded in 1889
The original workwear company built to serve and protect hardworking people
24/7
Europe
United
States
Asia
Pacific
Learn
More
Founded in 1989
Iconic Carhartt gear reinterpreted for those seeking refined design and style.
Europe
United States
Asia Pacific
Learn
More
Founded in 2019
Carhartt Company Gear™ is Carhartt's Commitment to serve hardworking business
United States
Learn
More
Discover
LOYALTY
Login
SignUp
Order Status
PHONE:
Monday - Friday
8:00 a.m. - 9:00 p.m. EST
Saturday - Sunday
Closed
LIVE CHAT:
Monday - Friday
9:00 a.m. - Midnight EST
Saturday - Sunday
9:00 a.m. - 9:00 p.m. EST
CHECK YOUR ORDER STATUS
CORPORATE ADDRESS:
Carhartt, Inc.
5750 Mercury Drive
Dearborn, MI 48126
Join/Log in Account
Learn About Groundbreakers
Member Exclusives
Discover Carhartt
Brands
History
Last Updated: November 29, 2017
We appreciate the trust you place in Carhartt, and we are committed to respecting your privacy and the security
of your personal information. This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for
www.carhartt.com. The statement does not include the privacy practices for partnered sites. We encourage our
users who visit external sites from links within Carhartt.com to read the privacy statements of those sites, as their
privacy practices may differ from ours and will govern their using your information. If you have questions or concerns
regarding this privacy policy, you should first contact us via
e-mail or by calling 1-800-833-3118. If you prefer to write us our postal address is below.
Carhartt Customer Service
P.O. Box 600
Dearborn, MI 48126
How We Disclose Personal Data
Carhartt will only disclose your Personal Data with your knowledge and as stated in this Privacy Policy or as indicated at the time of collection. This includes disclosures that will enable us to fulfill our obligations to you, and allows us to manage our business operations. We will only share your Personal Data with third parties in certain limited instances, namely with your consent, or as is necessary to complete a transaction or provide a product, service, or feature that you have requested.
We may disclose your Personal Data as described in this Privacy Policy and in the following ways:
To Affiliates, Partners, Vendors, and Suppliers
We share Personal Data among our Carhartt family of companies. We do this to run our business more efficiently and to have a better understanding of our Consumers across all of our business lines.
We also work with partners, vendors, distributors, and suppliers. These third parties may have access to or process your Personal Data, but only to the extent it is necessary for them to (1) provide their products and services to us, or (2) to provide you the products and services that you have requested. For example, we may use third-party providers to assist us with marketing and advertising our products and Services, delivering customer service and support (for example, when you have a question, complaint or technical issue with your account), and for e-commerce order fulfillment.
During Recruitment and Job Applications
When you submit an application for employment, we will collect your Personal information, including any information contained on a resume or curriculum vitae. This information is used worldwide to build our team as we look to hire talented teammates. We also may keep the information you submit in connection with an application for employment on file for future consideration.
To Enable the Use of Our Services
Personal Data that is collected through the Services may be used or disclosed to third parties in order to enable us to provide Services. For example, the Carhartt website may allow you to interface with a third-party website or application, such as PayPal or UPS.
In Community Forums
Any information you post or disclose in our community forums (for example, Facebook, BoldChat, YouTube, Twitter, Pinterest, Instagram, Olapic, Turn To, or other sponsored pages on the Carhartt Blog) is public. We cannot control the use of information disclosed in community forums, such as bulletin boards, blogs, chat rooms, and networking functions of mobile applications. Exercise caution when disclosing information in these public areas, and be careful what Personal Data you disclose and how you disclose it. Content posted in our community forums, including advice and opinions, represents the views of the individuals who post that Content and such individuals bear sole and exclusive responsibility for the posting of that content. Carhartt does not necessarily endorse, support, verify, or agree with any content posted in our Community Forums.
As We Grow and Change – Corporate Transactions and Reorganizations
If we should ever merge with another company, or if Carhartt should decide to buy, sell, or reorganize some part or all of its business, we may disclose or transfer, to the extent permitted by law and in compliance with any applicable requirements to notify you, your Personal Data to prospective or actual purchasers or successor entities in connection with one of these transactions or reorganizations.
As Required by Law and Special Circumstances
We may be required, subject to applicable law, to disclose your Personal Data if: (i) it is reasonably necessary to comply with legal process (such as a court order, subpoena, search warrant, etc.) or other legal requirements of any governmental authority, (ii) such a disclosure would potentially mitigate our liability in an actual or potential lawsuit, (iii) it is necessary to protect our legal rights or property, or (iv) it is necessary to protect the legal rights or property or physical security of others, or for the prevention or detection of crime and such disclosure is lawful.
Using Information We Collect
At Carhartt, we always want to provide you with the best possible shopping experience
and fulfill your orders exactly as you've requested. In order to do this, we collect
information that allows us to:
Process and track your order
Provide the services you request
Contact you about the status of an order
Send you catalogs or promotional offers we believe will be of interest to
you
Send you the Carhartt Email Newsletter, if requested
Identify your product and service preferences
Customize our communications to you (information shared with
our third party marketing partner to provide personalized
display advertising is made anonymous)
Improve our merchandise selection and customer service
Cookies
We regularly use technologies such as cookies. A "cookie"
is a small file stored by your web browser on your computer.
Cookies allow us to recognize who you are, when you arrive
at our site, by associating an anonymous identification
number in the cookie. At no time is your personally identifiable
information stored within one of our cookies.
We have selected an outside company, Omniture by Adobe,
to assist us in better understanding how people use our
site. Cookies will be placed on your computer to collect
non-personal information. The information that is collected
through these cookies tells us things like which search
engine referred you, how you navigated around our site,
what you browsed and purchased and what traffic is driven
by banner ads and emails. Carhartt.com does not allow
Omniture by Adobe to collect credit card, username or
password information.
provided by Carhartt,
click here.
Accepting cookies through your web browser is your personal
choice. You can set your browser to disable cookies.
We also contract with a third-party advertising partner
to serve ads on our behalf across the internet and sometimes
on this site. They will collect and use anonymous information
about your visits to and interactions with our website
through the use of technologies such as cookies to personalize
advertisements for goods and services which may appear
on other sites that you visit. To learn more, or to opt-out
of receiving advertisements tailored to your interests
by our third party partner, visit the Network Advertising
Initiative at www.networkadvertising.org/choices.
and, in most cases, an email with package tracking information.
If you decide to participate in our Field Testing Program
your email address will be used to send you surveys periodically.
Security
In our efforts to protect your information, Carhartt
uses a variety of technical safeguards, such as firewalls,
and we physically secure our servers.
In addition, when you make a purchase, request a catalog,
or create an account on our website, your information
is transmitted in an encrypted format.
The Carhartt.com website may contain links to other sites.
Carhartt does not control the use of personally identifiable
information on these websites. You should review the
privacy policies of every website before providing any
personal information. Carhartt is not responsible for
the conduct or practices of any linked websites. These
links are provided solely for the convenience and information
of our visitors.
Privacy of Children on Our Website
Our website is not intended for use by children under
the age of 13, and we do not knowingly collect personal
information from children under the age of 13.
Policy Changes
From time to time, we may use customer information for
unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy
policy notice. Before our information practices change,
we will post these changes on our website. We encourage
you to review our privacy policy periodically.
Questions or Comments?
For questions, comments or assistance, we invite you
to
contact us
We hope to answer any questions to your satisfaction,
Federal Trade Commission by phone at 202-FTC-HELP (202-382-4357
) or electronically at https://www.ftc.gov/ro/index.shtml
Chat with an ExpertX
